A Christmas Melody is a comedy, romance, tv movie film directed by Mariah Carey.
Kristin has just had to close her small Manhattan clothing boutique to return
to her Ohio home town and live in her parents' former home.
It's an adjustment for Kristin and her young daughter— especially
when she runs into her former high school rival.
Kristen and Emily struggle to find their new normal with
the help of the hunky local music teacher.
Kristin Frank, played by Lacey Chabert.
Danny Collier, played by Brennan Elliott.
Aunt Sarah, played by Kathy Najimy.
Melissa Atkinson, played by Mariah Carey.
Thomas, played by Kevin Chamberlin.
Emily Frank, played by Fina Strazza.
A Christmas Melody, also known under its working title of Mistletoe & Melody, is a 2015 American
Christmas television film directed by Mariah Carey, who co-stars with Lacey Chabert.
It was filmed in Ohio during October 2015, and premiered on
the Hallmark Channel on December 19, 2015.
The film was viewed by 3.95 million people upon its debut.
The film explores themes of woman director, christmas, christmas romance.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.